<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal on </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/personal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Professor Rahimian</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/testimonials/profrahimian/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/testimonials/profrahimian/</guid>
      <description>It is a pleasure to recommend such a distinguished individual as Mr. Omid Shenavar for graduate studies toward a Ph.D. degree. I have known Mr. Shenavar for seven years, since his admission to the MS program in Plant Pathology at Sari Agricultural Science and Natural Resources University (SANRU). He has been a student of mine in the plant pathogenic bacteria course, in which he ranked in the top five percent of over 160 students I have taught at SANRU and the University of Tehran, in the past 33 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who am I?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/bio/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;who-am-i&#34;&gt;Who am I?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hey there, I&amp;rsquo;m Omid Shenavar, a graduate of Shiraz University with a B.Sc. and SANRU with an M.Sc., where I dove into the fascinating world of plant protection and bacteriology. My studies have really ignited a passion for bacterial taxonomy, phylogeny, and biodiversity. But you know what? My hunger for knowledge in these areas is insatiable—I&amp;rsquo;m always up for learning more and broadening my horizons.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From day one, my dream has been to become a bona fide expert in plant bacteriology. That&amp;rsquo;s why I jumped at the chance to continue my studies at SANRU, guided by the legendary Professor Rahimian, a true rockstar in the world of phytobacteriology. Under his mentorship, my passion has only grown, and I&amp;rsquo;m incredibly grateful for his guidance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, I&amp;rsquo;m on a mission to snag a Ph.D. spot in plant bacteriology. My goal? To shake things up in the world of plant science with my research and expertise. I&amp;rsquo;m dead set on making an impact, and I won&amp;rsquo;t rest until I&amp;rsquo;ve reached the top of my game.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And hey, wanna see how determined I am? Check out these pics. The one from 2017? That&amp;rsquo;s where I started. But with some serious dedication and hard work, I&amp;rsquo;ve managed to shed over 50 kilograms. Talk about a transformation, right?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/beforeandnow.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;My Transformation&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;contact-me&#34;&gt;Contact Me&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:shenavar.omid@gmail.com&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://img.icons8.com/fluency/48/000000/gmail.png&#34; alt=&#34;Email&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
